Guide to the Julia Driver Collection of Women in Photography
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Card Photographs and Other Photographic Materials, 1845-1940; Series II; 5.83
  - Photographic Materials
    - Bertolacci, Misses, circa 1870; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 3, Folder 70)
      Partnership of sisters Caroline Cecilia Cobham Bertolacci (1840-1889), Marie Eliza Cobham Bertolacci (1843-1929), and Ida Louisa Clara Cobham Bertolacci (born 1844)
      Active in London, England, 1865-1891
    - Bieber, Emilie, Madame (1810-1884), circa 1866-1874; (4 cartes-de-visite) (Box 3, Folder 71)
      Active in Hamburg, Germany, 1852-1872
      Also known as Madame E. Bieber
    - Bird, Sarah Jane Sherman, Mrs., circa 1872; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 3, Folder 72)
      Active in Mineral Point, Wisconsin, circa 1872
      Also known as Mrs. S. Bird or Mrs. Benjamin Franklin Bird
    - Bissell, Cynthia Miriam Spofford, Mrs. (1810-1899), circa 1870; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 3, Folder 73)
      Active in Tecumseh, Michigan, circa 1844-1899
      Also known as Mrs. C. M. Bissell or Mrs. Theodore Bissell
    - Blom, Alma, 1897; (1 cabinet photograph) (Box 3, Folder 74)
      Active in Stockholm, Sweden, circa 1897-1910
      Portrait of Peter J. Palmer posed sitting with another man and drinking
    - Bökman, Sophie, circa 1885-1890; (1 cabinet photograph) (Box 3, Folder 75)
      Active in Halmstad, Sweden, circa 1885-1890
    - Bone, Marie, circa 1900; (1 cabinet photograph) (Box 3, Folder 76)
      Active in Fakenham and Norwich, England, circa 1900
    - Borel, Mary, Miss (born 1882), 1898; (1 cabinet photograph) (Box 3, Folder 77)
      Active in San Antonio, Texas, 1898
      Also known as Miss M. Borel or Mrs. Joseph Solsona
      Portrait of Dolores Llanas (born 1888)
    - Bosanquet, Madame, circa 1867; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 3, Folder 78)
      Active in Cork, Ireland, circa 1867
    - Bowen, G. M., Mrs., circa 1886; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 3, Folder 79)
      Active in Elroy, Wisconsin, circa 1886
    - Bowles, Esther A. Buck, Mrs. (born 1852), circa 1892; (1 cabinet photograph) (Box 3, Folder 80)
      Active in Wyandotte, Michigan, 1892-1921
      Also known as Mrs. E. A. Bowles and Mrs. George A. Bowles
      Group portrait of a brass band comprised of three men and three women.
    - Bradley, E. Ogden, Mrs., circa 1885; (2 cabinet photographs) (Box 4, Folder 81)
      Active in Corfu, New York, circa 1885
      Also known as Mrs. Emma Ogden Bradley, Mrs. Emily Ogden Bradley, or Mrs. Robert O. Bradley
    - Bradley, Lena, Miss, 1896-1899; (1 cabinet photograph) (Box 4, Folder 82)
      Active in Attica and Caldwell, Kansas, 1896-1899
      Portrait of two men posed with tennis rackets and a tennis net
    - Brecht, Emily, Mrs. (born circa 1850), 1867-1875; (2 cartes-de-visite and 1 cabinet photograph) (Box 4, Folder 83)
      Active in Saint Louis, Missouri, 1867-1875
      Also known as Amelia Brecht, Mrs. Gustave V. Brecht, or the Saint Louis Double-Light Photograph Gallery
      Includes a portrait of a bride and groom, as well as a portrait of a woman with a dog
    - Brennan, Lydia L., Mrs., 1890-1898; (2 cabinet photographs and 1 piece of ephemera) (Box 4, Folder 84)
      Active in Butte, Montana, 1890-1898
      Also known as Mrs. L. L. Brennan or the Elite Studio
      Includes a sheet of stationery from the Elite Studio for an order for negatives from the A. M. Holter Hardware Company in Helena, Montana, written and signed by Brennan on April 2, 1896
    - Brewster, L. E., Mrs., circa 1866; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 4, Folder 85)
      Active in Monroe, Wisconsin, circa 1866
    - Bridgman, Mary Jane Holmes, Mrs., circa 1870; (2 cartes-de-visite) (Box 4, Folder 86)
      Active in Amboy and Franklin Grove, Illinois, as well as Oswego, Kansas, circa 1860-1879
      Also known as Mrs. C. T. Bridgman or Mrs. Cyrus T. Bridgman
      Includes a portrait of Catherine Harding (born 1826) or Amboy, Illinois
    - Briginshaw, Elizabeth Apperly, Mrs. (1818-1901), 1865; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 4, Folder 87)
      Active in Tewkesbury, England, 1863-1865
      Also known as Mrs. Isaac Briginshaw
    - Brock, Mary, Miss (born circa 1833), circa 1867; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 4, Folder 88)
      Active in Greencastle, Indiana, circa 1867
    - Brockway, Emily Hyde, Mrs. (1848-1928), circa 1900; (2 cabinet photographs) (Box 4, Folder 89)
      Active in Wellsville, Kansas, 1899-1920
      Also known as Mrs. E. Brockway, Mrs. Milla Brockway, Mrs. W. S. Brockway or Mrs. William Spencer Brockway
    - Broom, Christina Livingston, Mrs. (1863-1939), 1908; (3 photographic postcards) (Box 4, Folder 90)
      Active in London, England, 1903-1939
      Also known as Mrs. Albert Broom
      Includes a exterior portrait of King Edward VII and his family at the Duke of York's Royal Military School in Dover, Kent, 1908, as well as a view of a Clydesdale horse, Black Prince, with a groom, circa 1908
    - Brown, Ada, Miss (born circa 1850), 1872-1874; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 4, Folder 91)
      Active in Memphis, Tennessee, 1872-1874
    - Brown, B. A., Miss, circa 1866; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 4, Folder 92)
      Active in Camden, New York, circa 1866
    - Brown, Caroline, Mrs. (born 1844), circa 1880-1890; (2 cartes-de-visite) (Box 4, Folder 93)
      Active in Burr Oak, Howell, and Lockport, Michigan, circa 1880-1890
      Also known as Mrs. M. Brown or Mrs. Mark Brown
    - Brown, Ella L., circa 1890; (1 cabinet photograph) (Box 4, Folder 94)
      Active in Burr Oak, Michigan, circa 1890
    - Brown, Mary, Mrs., circa 1895; (1 cabinet photograph) (Box 4, Folder 95)
      Active in Cainsville, Missouri, circa 1895
      Also known as Barton's Gallery
    - Browning, Teresa Dessurne, Mrs., 1864-1869; (3 cartes-de-visite) (Box 4, Folder 96)
      Active in Glasgow, Scotland, 1864-1869
      Also known as Mrs. William Browning
    - Bryant, Kate Morris, Mrs. (born 1863), circa 1890; (1 carte-de-visite and 3 cabinet photographs) (Box 4, Folder 97)
      Active in Indianapolis, Indiana, 1889-1920
      Also known as Mrs. Katie Bryant, Mrs. D. C. Bryant, or Mrs. David C. Bryant
      Includes a portrait of Rosa Minger Schwab (1872-1892)
    - Buck, Ella L., Mrs. (born 1857), circa 1885; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 4, Folder 98)
      Active in Fort Atkinson and Koshkonong, Wisconsin, 1882-1904
      Also known as Mrs. Almond B. Buck
    - Budge, Maria Palmer Richards, Mrs. (born circa 1830), circa 1861; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 4, Folder 99)
      Active in Wells, England, circa 1861
      Also known as Mrs. John Budge
    - Buell, Susie, Mrs. (born 1864), circa 1890; (2 cabinet photographs) (Box 4, Folder 100)
      Active in Marrowbone, Kentucky, circa 1900
      Also known as Buell & Wife or Mrs. Frank Buell
      Includes a portrait of the Cheatham family
    - Bulmer, Fannie, Mrs. (1839-1922), 1887; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 4, Folder 101)
      Active in Flesherton, Canada, 1886-1900
      Also known as Mrs. William Bulmer
      Portrait of Alfred Deforrest Skidmore Thurston (1872-1944)
    - Burnett, Lou, Miss, 1895-1896; (1 cabinet photograph) (Box 4, Folder 102)
      Active in Humeston, Iowa, 1895-1896
    - Burt, L. S., Mrs., 1891-1892; (2 cabinet photographs) (Box 4, Folder 103)
      Active in Fresno, California, 1891-1892
    - Bush, Martha, Miss (born 1862), circa 1900; (1 card photograph) (Box 4, Folder 104)
      Active in Aurora, Indiana, circa 1900
    - Bustin, Marian, Mrs. (born circa 1837), circa 1865-1870; (5 cartes-de-visite) (Box 4, Folder 105)
      Active in Hereford and Ross-on-Wye, England, circa 1860-1900
      Also known as Mrs. Richard Britton Bustin
      Includes a view of a building, identified as the Brook House
    - Cadwell, Lydia J., circa 1880; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 4, Folder 106)
      Active in Chicago, Illinois, 1879-1881
      Also known as the Gentile and Lydian Art Gallery
    - Cady, Lovonia, Mrs. (1837-1918), circa 1870; (5 cartes-de-visite) (Box 4, Folder 107)
      Active in Waitsfield, Vermont, circa 1860-1880
      Also known as Mrs. H. B. Cady or Mrs. Henry Boyce Cady
      Includes a portrait of Martha Davis (born circa 1801) of Duxbury, Vermont
    - Carlton, C. T., Mrs. (born circa 1836), circa 1866; (1 tintype) (Box 4, Folder 108)
      Active in Birmingham, Michigan, 1865-1867
    - Carr, Mary Elizabeth Corbin, Mrs. (born circa 1862), circa 1885-1888; (2 cabinet photographs) (Box 4, Folder 109)
      Active in Wymore, Nebraska, circa 1885-1888
      Also known as Mrs. H. S. Carr, Mrs. Harland S. Carr, or Mrs. William Needham
    - Carrick, Misses, circa 1870; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 4, Folder 110)
      Active in Newcastle upon Tyne, England, 1869-1880
      Partnership between sisters Jane Carrick (born circa 1841) and Mina Carrick (born circa 1846)
    - Carruthers, Katherine, Mrs. (born 1870), circa 1910; (1 photographic print) (Box 4, Folder 111)
      Active in San Jose, California, 1899-1920
      Also known as Mrs. William J. Carruthers
    - Carter, Ida E., Mrs. (born circa 1850), circa 1900; (1 piece of ephemera) (Box 4, Folder 112)
      Active in Lowville, New York, circa 1880-1920
      Also known as Mrs. G. W. Carter or Mrs. George W. Carter
    - Catlin, Mabel C., Miss (born 1881), circa 1900; (1 card photograph) (Box 4, Folder 113)
      Active in Lynch, Nebraska, circa 1900
      Portrait of Sadie Harvey (born 1882) of Gross, Nebraska
    - Chapman, Flora C., Miss (born 1868), 1903 November 6; (1 cabinet photograph) (Box 4, Folder 114)
      Active in Sullivan, Illinois, circa 1900
      Exterior portrait of a man with a racehorse owned by A. F. Miller of Sullivan, Illinois, probably at a racetrack in Springfield, Illinois
    - Chappell, Eliza B., Mrs., 1884-1889; (2 cabinet photographs) (Box 4, Folder 115)
      Active in Sturgis, Michigan, 1884-1889
      Also known as Mrs. E. B. Chappell
    - Charles, Julia O., Mrs. (born 1857), circa 1900; (1 cabinet photograph) (Box 4, Folder 116)
      Active in Salamanca, New York, circa 1900-1930
      Also known as Mrs. David Charles
    - Chase, Belle Bybee, Mrs. (born 1863), circa 1900; (3 card photographs) (Box 4, Folder 117)
      Active in Los Angeles, California, and Denver, Colorado, 1898-1921
      Also known as Mrs. B. B. Chase or Mrs. C. F. Chase,
    - Chenoweth, Annie Agnes Wayne, Mrs. (born circa 1856), 1890; (2 cabinet photographs) (Box 4, Folder 118)
      Active in Atlanta, Illinois, circa 1890-1910
      Also known as Mrs. A. W. Chenoweth or Mrs. Alfred W. Chenoweth
      Memorial card for Marion P. Hieronymus (1869-1890)
    - Christoffersen, Dina, circa 1890; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 4, Folder 119)
      Active in Halden (Frederikshald), Norway, circa 1890
    - Chytræus, Augusta Aurora, (1853-1921), circa 1887-1904; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 4, Folder 120)
      Active in Göteborg and Åmål, Norway, circa 1887-1904
    - Clairville, Marie, circa 1890; (1 cabinet photograph) (Box 4, Folder 121)
      Active in Vienna, Austria, circa 1890
    - Clark, Emma A., Mrs. (born circa 1852), circa 1880; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 4, Folder 122)
      Active in Buffalo, New York, circa 1880
    - Clark, Savilla, Mrs. (born 1849), circa 1880; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 4, Folder 123)
      Active in York, Nebraska, circa 1880
      Also known as Mrs. D. G. Clark or Mrs. Dan G. Clark
    - Clegg, Mary A., (born circa 1850), circa 1880; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 4, Folder 124)
      Active in Darlington, Wisconsin, circa 1880
    - Clizbe Sisters, 1895-1906; (4 cabinet photographs) (Box 4, Folder 125)
      Partnership between sisters Carrie E. Clizbe (1859-1921), later Mrs. Herbert H. Webb, and Martha Clizbe (1864-1906)
      Active in Reedsburg, Wisconsin, 1895-1906
      Includes a portrait of Edna Swetland (born 1878) in 1900
    - Clough, Cynthia J., Mrs. (circa 1843-circa 1896), circa 1892-1894; (1 cabinet photograph) (Box 4, Folder 126)
      Active in West Somerville, Massachusetts, circa 1892-1894
      Also known as Mrs. C. J. Clough or Mrs. Benjamin Clough
    - Coan, M. J., Mrs. (born circa 1849), circa 1880; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 4, Folder 127)
      Active in Medicine Lodge, Kansas, circa 1880
      Also known as Mrs. S. P. Coan or the Star Photo Gallery
    - Collier, Adelia M., Mrs. (born circa 1831), circa 1860-1869; (3 cartes-de-visite) (Box 4, Folder 128)
      Active in Circleville, Ohio, circa 1860-1869
      Also known as Mrs. M. A. Collier, Mrs. Albert J. Collier, Collier & Haddock, or Collier & Mix
      Includes a portrait of Elliott Marfield (1862-1911) and his sister, Harriet E. Marfield (circa 1863-1942), circa 1868
    - Collins, Mary, Mrs., circa 1865; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 4, Folder 129)
      Active in Boonville, Missouri, circa 1865
    - Collins, Sarah, Mrs. (born circa 1831), circa 1868; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 4, Folder 130)
      Active in Macomb, Ohio, 1868-1879
      Also known as Mrs. Collins or Mrs. Andrew Collins
    - Condon, Linnie, Mrs. (circa 1844-1909), circa 1898; (2 cabinet photographs and 1 card photograph) (Box 4, Folder 131)
      Active in Atlanta, Georgia, 1883-1908
      Also known as Mrs. Thomas F. Condon, Mrs. Ambrose L. Hendricks, or Mrs. L. Condon-Hendricks
      Portraits of Kitty Van Dyke Anderson (born 1871), the wife of Clifford LeConte Anderson (1862-1933)
    - Cone, Maria Union, Mrs. (born circa 1851), circa 1880; (1 cabinet photograph) (Box 4, Folder 132)
      Active in Farmington, Illinois, circa 1880
      Also known as Mrs. J. C. Cone or Mrs. Joseph C. Cone
    - Conroy, Sarah Jane, Mrs., circa 1871; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 4, Folder 133)
      Active in Valletta, Malta, circa 1871
      Also known as Mrs. James Conroy
      Composite portrait of a sailor with the phrase, "Remember me, forget me not"
    - Cooper, Susan D. Hudnut, Mrs. (born circa 1822), circa 1860; (6 cartes-de-visite) (Box 4, Folder 134)
      Active in Maysville, Kentucky, circa 1860-1869
      Also known as Mrs. R. Cooper, Mrs. Robert Cooper, or Mrs. R. Cooper & Son
      Includes portraits of Thomas Browning (born circa 1833) and his wife, Preshea A. Browning (born circa 1841)
    - Corbyn, Mrs., circa 1869; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 5, Folder 135)
      Active in London, England, circa 1869
    - Cornand, Gonthier, Madame, circa 1875; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 5, Folder 136)
      Active in Liège, Belgium, circa 1875
    - Cornell, Minerva, Mrs. (born 1832), circa 1870-1880; (23 cartes-de-visite and 22 stereographs) (Box 5, Folder 137)
      Active in Lodi and Waterloo, New York, circa 1870-1880
      Also known as Mrs. M. Cornell, Mrs. C. V. D. Cornell, or Mrs. Cornelius V. D. Cornell
      Includes a carte-de-visite portrait of Omer Huff (born circa 1837)
      Stereographs of Waterloo, New York include interior and exterior views of the Towsley House Hotel; interior views of the Saint John Chapel, and discrete views of Saint Paul's Church and Main Street
      Several stereographs depict Minerva Cornell with a model of the residence of Reverend Henry G. Dewitt (born 1835) in Canandaigua, New York, which she made from seashells.
      Two stereographs depict a memorial floral display for Anna Hollenbach (died 1885).
      Another stereograph is a copy photograph of a bird's eye lithograph engraving of the Willard Asylum for the Chronic Insane in Willard, New York
    - Cottrell, Mary Ellen Larkam, Mrs. (1845-1908), circa 1865; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 5, Folder 138)
      Active in Oregon, Missouri, circa 1861-1880
      Also known as Mrs. D. E. Cottrell, Mrs. Daniel Ellington Cotrell, Mrs. Mary Clyde, Mrs. Mary Tanner, or Mrs. Sylvanus Webster Tanner
    - Cowen, E. M., Miss, circa 1890; (1 cabinet photograph) (Box 5, Folder 139)
      Active in Webster, Waubay, South Dakota, circa 1890
    - Cox, J. R., Mrs., circa 1860; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 5, Folder 140)
      Active in Sterling, Illinois, circa 1860
    - Crane, Maria Ann, Mrs., 1893; (2 cabinet photographs) (Box 5, Folder 141)
      Active in Prairie City, Illinois, circa 1893
      Also known as Miss A. M. Crane or Ann Crane
      Includes a portrait of Oliver Claire Mings (born 1893)
    - Critcher, Charla, Miss (1874-1961), 1900; (1 cabinet photograph) (Box 5, Folder 142)
      Active in Bolivar, Missouri, 1900
    - Cronise, Anna Louise, (1865-1944), circa 1905; (3 cabinet photographs) (Box 5, Folder 143)
      Active in Portland and Salem, Oregon, circa 1890-1920
      Also known as Mrs. Anna Cronise Trover or Mrs. Howard Trover
      Includes a portrait of a bride and groom, as well as a girl dressed for her first communion
    - Crusius, Carrie M., Miss, 1863 November-December; (2 cartes-de-visite) (Box 5, Folder 144)
      Active in Indianapolis, Indiana, circa 1863
      Includes portraits of her employee, Daniel H. Pennewill (born 1835) and his wife, Susan Fannie Wood Pennewill
    - Culié, Katharina, 1900; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 5, Folder 145)
      Active in Frankfurt, Germany, circa 1884-1900
    - Cutler, Mariah A., Mrs. (circa 1828), 1868-1884; (30 cartes-de-visite, 1 tintype, and 1 cabinet photograph) (Box 5, Folder 146)
      Active in Dixon and Galva, Illinois, as well as Chariton and Creston, Iowa, 1868-1884
      Also known as Mrs. M. A. Cutler or Mrs. Elias D. Cutler
      Includes two cartes-de-visite by her son, William H. Cutler (born circa 1847)
    - Cuyler, Harriet E., Mrs. (born 1853), circa 1891; (2 cabinet photographs) (Box 5, Folder 147)
      Active in Mount Clemens, Michigan, 1886-1927
      Also known as Mrs. William Benjamin Cuyler or Mrs. Ben Cuyler
      Includes a portrait of Frederick A. Drexel (born 1856), a jeweler
    - Dahlberg, Anna, circa 1895-1900; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 5, Folder 148)
      Active in Falkenberg, Sweden, circa 1895-1900
    - Dahlberg, Lydia, 1897-1903; (7 cartes-de-visite) (Box 5, Folder 149)
      Active in Örnsköldsvik, Sweden, 1897-1903
    - De Wolf, Harriet A., Mrs. (born circa 1832), circa 1860-1865; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 5, Folder 150)
      Active in Franklin, Pennsylvania, circa 1860-1865
      Also known as Mrs. Isaac S. P. De Wolf
    - Decker, Julia English, Mrs. (born circa 1839), circa 1865; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 5, Folder 151)
      Active in Cleveland, Ohio, circa 1860-1869
      Also known as Mrs. Edgar Decker
      Portrait of Sally Miner (born circa 1875), a tailor from Williamsfield and Mayfield, Ohio
    - Deisting, Sophie, circa 1880; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 5, Folder 152)
      Active in Mölln, Germany, circa 1880
    - Denton, Harriet, Mrs. (born 1852), circa 1880; (1 cabinet photograph) (Box 5, Folder 153)
      Active in Newton, Kansas, circa 1880
      Also known as Mrs. B. F. Denton or Mrs. B. Frank Denton
    - Dexter, Sarah, Mrs. (born circa 1826-1895), circa 1865; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 5, Folder 154)
      Active in Lynn, England, circa 1865
      Also known as Mrs. Walter Sothern Dexter
    - Dixon, Ellenor Humphreys, Mrs. (born circa 1825), circa 1866; (2 cartes-de-visite) (Box 5, Folder 155)
      Active in Lymington, England, circa 1861-1871
      Also known as Mrs. Ellen Dixon or Mrs. John Porter Dixon
    - Doolittle, Sarah K., Miss (1854-1925), circa 1878-1882; (2 cartes-de-visite) (Box 5, Folder 156)
      Active in Belvidere, Illinois, as well as Beloit, Wisconsin, circa 1878-1882
      Also known as Miss S. K. Doolittle or Mrs. Lemuel Hooper Schurman
    - Downing, Marionette Hummel, Mrs. (born 1868), circa 1900-1910; (1 cabinet photograph and 1 card photograph) (Box 5, Folder 157)
      Active in Juneau, Wisconsin, circa 1900-1910
      Also known as Mrs. W. J. Downing or Mrs. William J. Downing
    - Dukelow, Margaret Jane, Miss (born 1865), circa 1895; (1 cabinet photograph) (Box 5, Folder 158)
      Active in Iroquois, Canada, circa 1890-circa 1905
      Also known as Miss M. J. Dukelow or Mrs. Harry Bryant
    - Durham, Susan, Mrs. (born 1831), circa 1870; (3 cartes-de-visite) (Box 5, Folder 159)
      Active in Prairie City, Illinois, circa 1868-1878
      Also known as Mrs. S. Durham
      Portrait of E. J. Lockwood, founder of the Prairie City Baptist Church
    - Durston, Lizzie, circa 1888; (1 cabinet photograph) (Box 5, Folder 160)
      Active in Cummings and Bisbee, North Dakota, circa 1888
      View of a general store owned by Ole G. Skalet (born 1853) and Thomas T. Shell (born 1857) in Rolla, North Dakota
    - Edlund, Anna, 1900; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 5, Folder 161)
      Active in Stockholm, Sweden, 1889-1905
    - Edwards, Ada Walton, Mrs. (born 1860), circa 1895; (1 cabinet photograph) (Box 5, Folder 162)
      Active in New Sharon, Iowa, circa 1890-1910
      Also known as Mrs. F. C. Walton or Mrs. Frank C. Edwards
    - Elite Studio, circa 1896; (1 cabinet photograph) (Box 5, Folder 163)
      Partnership of Margaret M. Foster (born 1867) and Minnie K. Wachtman (born 1868)
      Active in Spokane, Washington, circa 1896-1932
    - Elliott, Letitia E., Mrs. (born circa 1845), circa 1870-1880; (3 cartes-de-visite) (Box 5, Folder 164)
      Active in Streator, Illinois, circa 1870-1880
      Also known as Mrs. Robert Elliot
      Includes a portrait of three boys, which includes a set of twins
    - Emery, Henrietta, Miss (1833-1891), circa 1860-1869; (4 cartes-de-visite) (Box 5, Folder 165)
      Active in Bryan, Ohio, circa 1860-1869
      Also known as Miss H. Emery or Mrs. Albert Elliot
    - Ensminger, Clara A., Miss (born 1859), 1888-1906; (1 cabinet photograph and 2 card photographs) (Box 5, Folder 166)
      Active in Hyde and Yuma, Colorado, as well as Toledo, Iowa, 1888-1906
      Includes a portrait of Zelma Mae Filloon (1905-1926) in 1906
    - Ersly, H. Elizabeth, Mrs. (born circa 1840), 1878-1880; (9 cartes-de-visite) (Box 5, Folder 167)
      Active in Whitewater, Wisconsin, 1878-1880
      Also known as Mrs. H. Elizabeth Ersley or Mrs. Perry Ersly
      Includes portraits of Mary Green (born circa 1868) and Vira A. Brockway (born circa 1853)
    - Esterbrook, Harriet Austin Leary, Mrs. (circa 1856-1933), circa 1880-1885; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 5, Folder 168)
      Active in Peterborough, Canada, circa 1880-1885
      Also known as Mrs. Thomas Esterbrook or Mrs. George James Early
    - Evans, Jane, Mrs., circa 1870; (2 cartes-de-visite) (Box 5, Folder 169)
      Active in Fredonia, New York, circa 1870
      Also known as Mrs. O. B. Evans or Mrs. Oliver Benton Evans
      Includes a portrait of Edgar Colson (born circa 1845)
    - Faulhaber, Lillie Grimshaw, Mrs. (born 1842), circa 1880; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 5, Folder 170)
      Active in Sedalia, Missouri, circa 1880
      Also known as Mrs. G. L. Faulhaber or Mrs. George Ludwig Faulhaber
    - Faunce, Lydia Buck, Mrs. (born circa 1845), circa 1870; (2 cartes-de-visite) (Box 5, Folder 171)
      Active in Franklin Grove, Illinois, circa 1860-1870
      Also known as Mrs. E. E. Faunce or Mrs. Edwin E. Faunce
    - Fay, Mrs., circa 1890; (1 cabinet photograph) (Box 5, Folder 172)
      Active in Blyth, Canada, circa 1890
      Location misspelled "Btlyh" on verso
    - Fehrenbach, Isabel Elisha, Madame (1831-1877), circa 1870-1877; (3 cartes-de-visite) (Box 5, Folder 173)
      Includes discrete portraits of sisters Sarah Mary Disson (born circa 1850) and Charlotte Tyler Disson (born circa 1854), circa 1877
    - Fessenden, Mary Righter, Mrs. (1833-1928), circa 1860-1869; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 5, Folder 174)
      Active in Twinsburg, Ohio, circa 1860-1869
      Also known as Mrs. J. W. Fessenden or Mrs. John W. Fessenden
    - Field, Ann, Mrs. (born circa 1828), circa 1870; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 5, Folder 175)
      Active in Hounslow, England, 1860-circa 1891
      Also known as Mrs. Mortimer Field
    - Fields, Margaret J. McGinley, Mrs. (born circa 1828), circa 1855-1890; (9 cartes-de-visite and 1 cabinet photograph) (Box 5, Folder 176)
      Active in Burlington and Lyons, Iowa, circa 1855-1890